We do.  Who will win, who will
lose?  And which government this time?
First ball wide here.
And that's a good strike high in the air
and well taken.
That's the big fish in to the pavilion.
That's a big break through here for the team
Alliance Strikers Mangesh Jagtap
departs.
Good catch again by Prasad
Nitin
so big of relief for the team
and two runs taken
Nitin Nikam the double n first ball
striking for two runs they have
a big batting line up Warriors
not only one player Mangesh Jagtap they have
p of hard hit batsman
no runs taken sent back already almost the
batter non sticker batter went at the half track
sent back
oh wow wow is that out.   Yes.
Good catch taken.
Reminds him of being a catch of the match and
Mohammad Kaif has taken a similar catch but
not beyond the stumps.
But the good work by beyond the stumps by
MSD.
That's Sanjay MSD for you.
Four balls three two Prent Warriors
now they are in trouble.
Om
just a single played towards sh third man
Sachin and Akshay
this two batsmen
a big responsibility on their shoulders to set
up a big score on the board lost two
wickets early in the very first over
and that's a good strike high in the air
Prasad once again that could be
the catch of the tournament.  It was
almost a 20 meters running for him.
Friends, there should be a big round of applause for But Prasad.  Good attempt to take that.
So one was gone five for two prone warriors.
Om
one was gone five for two Pran Warriors once
again Satyan Singh
change in the field settings
one fielder at mid wicket on one at deep
extra cover
just guiding the ball down towards third man
and that will go all the way for four runs the
fielder tried a bit of messy football
skills applied but the effort went in won went
for four runs
three overs match
1.19 for two with the boundary.
Once again we have trending Akshay Dhurandhar
on strike.
It's very good keeping also down the leg
for wide
Satyan Singh need to come back in this over
just going outside the off line for wide one more wide six
runs came in one ball only
11 for two this
time got the outside fielder third man
only a single run rotating the strike both
the batsmen Sachin and Akshay
already seven runs they can go for some big
hits seven runs of the over so far two balls
only bowled
this is a time for the team Proud
Warriors to get many runs in this over.   That's
a good strike.  They will go for two.
Two Rans Taken.
Bit a fumble at the fielder at long off.
And good running by Sachin
it's a bit of in the air
direct throw but two runs taken excellent
running between the wickets
back to back two runs
1.46 pe do and I think Pudent
Warriors seem to have eaten Puneri mixture.  You did
not bring me here.
Amazing Puneri Mixture
16 for two
Only a single
17 for two
12 of the over Last ball coming up of the
second
and the keeper misses
That will go for four By
expensive over came
almost 16 runs I was talking about they can get many
runs
and that's what happened
16 of the over after two overs 21 for two
Prent Warriors
two overs gone 21 for two and last over
coming up
two shut 21 raid two gadi after Prent Warriors
it's a last
over of the first innings
Kaushik that's a
good strike Every ball is getting
cheered and the dug out and that's what the
energy motivation needed and that's what
Prent Warriors this is not just
a cricket it's the festival
carnival and they are celebrating in style
22 for two with one run Last five balls of this
first innings
and that's gone for wide They
going for two runs o
great effort
Previous ball
umpire previous ball that was dot ball right
previous ball was dot ball previous ball was
wide
2.2 it's 25 for two last four balls coming
up last four balls
prod warriors
and let's see if they can go for two runs but
the striker batsman may be got some
hurt there he will be
retired out may be Kiran is going
retired hurt
ok last three balls coming up 26 for two
excellent bowling there is a big shout is that
run out yes that's out
last two balls coming up of the first
innings 26 for three
oh very good bowling from Kaushik
and one wicket only five runs have been given
in five balls.
26 for four
Krishanjeet
13 number jersey on his back the new batsman walks in
last ball first innings have to see wicket
single two runs four runs six runs what will happen
or dot ball
spot down the leg side
wide 27
and one ball here Kaushik will have to go for run up.
And to Rans Taken.
So, after three overs, Alliance Strikers are 29 for four and need 30 runs.
It's time for the next four teams in
Group C and may I request captain
from Unison Superstar Star vs Anand
Rathi United for the
toss come
Anand Rathi United Captain
and Unison Superstar
toss ka boss
and may I request from the official
for the comment anyone
Unison Superstar Captain welcome come
Eknath so welcome to the ICICI Lomb
Brokers Premier League 2026 third edition how is
the feeling you are going to play
first match
or it's our first match so basically we are little because
last year also we have faced
Anand Rathi and we have faced a loss also
with them.  So this time we will be trying
to
beat them.  Letts C.  Okay so Unison
Superstars how's a josh?
Vary Lo.  How is a josh?
What is the matter.  Wow wow.  Ananda Ra United
First Match.  How is the feeling?  How is the
excitement?
It's great.  This is our second time that we are
playing this tournament.  So it's a
great initiative.  Nice to meet people in the
same industry.  It's a good, I mean
sports always is a good way to connect
with everybody.
Yeah, absolutely.  Anand Ratri United
Make Some Noise.
Let's declare the Anand Ratri team a win-win.
Ok.   Who
will call?  Unison and Anand Ratri Unison
Will Call Heads Is The Call
Tails It is you want the toss, what you
decided and why?
We will feel first.  It's good, I mean I know we have
a very strong bowling line
up.  So we will be able to restrict them
and chase the total.
Okay, I wish you all the best and Unison
Superstar what do you think in five overs a
big target to set for the team Anand Rati
United.
Or, uh we'll be trying to set a target
of around 55 60 plus.  Let's see then.  Thank
you.
Okay, I wish you all the best, both the
captains.
So the team
Younis and Superstar they one the toss decided
to bowl first stay tune for the live
action coming up first match of group C
ok umpire requested to get speed up
a bit faster
Mumbai had time because
they say time is money money is
time money is time time is money
om
so the target of 30 to chase for the team Aion
Strikers
group B
last match and we are group C now first
match coming up after this match and four teams have
joined us.  So welcome to the
ICICI Lombard Brokers Premier League
26. The four teams joining us are Unison
Superstar Anand R.A. United One All One Team
and S Diamonds.
This time he lifted the ball in the air and took a very
simple catch.
Fall of wicket.
First ball, wicket, second ball, wicket.
Their cricket is amazing.
Back to back wickets.
Target of 30 here. But they say
low scoring game.
More drama. But you can say 10 runs
per over is not easy. And now coming up is the
hat-trick. Ball for Ashish Mishra. Deepesh
on strike. We have to
see if Ashish Mishra will become the
first
player to take a hat-trick in this tournament.
Here we go. Toss is
good. Stop by fielder
only for a single. Deepesh is
off the mark. Now Rishikesh will face the
first ball.
So left-right combination
will burn the calories.
Setting of the field. Mangesh Jagtap.
Now for the left-hander. Other two fielders are deep
backward. Again deep mid-wicket.
And that's a good strike. But there is a
fielder standing and excellent field set
up by the  Skipper
just a single
four balls two on two alien strikers
so once again welcome in the com box Mr
Om Sir how are you feeling the
match is going very well Ashish is bowling very well let's
see the batsman ran for two runs and at the same time a
very good throw
and a run out is taking place it
seems Mangesh Jagtap has aimed more at the throw
he wanted to hit it directly
absolutely so along
with a good batsman you have a
good fielder bowler and an all rounder contender
how can you say
super dhamaka
full complete package Mangesh
three runs and three wickets in five balls.
First over ends, three on four,
two overs, 26 runs needed.
Bowler Mangesh
and Rishi on strike, Satyan on non-strike,
last
among us, Nirav Sir,
famous cricketer of
Titans,
yes absolutely Nirav Bheda, has scored 15000 runs
till now, is giving tough fight to Virat Kohli in his entire career
and there was a chance of run out but Rishi put in all his effort
in running,
Satyan is on strike, let's see
how Mangesh plays, Mangesh
is a good all-rounder,
next ball is of Mangesh and he played it in the air,
Mangesh got under the ball and a very easy
catch.
So the way we started here,
President Warriors have made a good start by giving five runs and losing four
wickets,
30 runs to win here,
but look at that bowling
and
Mangesh, while
bowling well, made a
bit hasty team and lost four wickets
and this fifth wicket also in the block hole,
excellent bowling by Mangesh that was a yorker and
delivery toe crusher directly on the stumps, Mangesh
started from where Ashish had left
and Mangesh also lived up to
his captain's
score, look at the score on the left hand side,
this is not a football game.  Fay all ya fay
for fire.
And now Mangesh is on a hat-trick.
Three balls remaining in this over.  Next ball from Mangesh.   A
shot played on the on side.  The fielder behind will have to be
satisfied with just one run.
Two balls remaining in this over.
1.4 balls,
six runs, five wickets.
Now the sage has come.  If the match is to be won then Rishi will have to hit
two big hits.  And
look, it seems it has hit big.   No no no, I
lacked a little strength Rishi,
a little strength, very good catch,
three wickets here in the name of Mangesh,
I had already said that
Mangesh started from where Ashish had left.
Ashish had taken three wickets and now Mangesh also
took three wickets in that over, yes exactly three wickets, so the balance sheet has been
tallied.  Yes, 1.5 six
needed 24 runs in seven balls, Kaushik is the new
batsman.
He will have to hit four powerful hits.  Om Sir,
yes, the
left hand had a slight advantage.   The
sage tried his best but failed.   A
very good catch here and this wide ball is
signalled by umpire Navsad.
Last ball of this over was bowled by Mangesh.
Good binges happened here.  Let's give a
big round of applause to Mangesh.
One over, three for three, what a thing, give
a round of
applause, come on,
after two overs, six for seven,
23 runs needed, six balls, 23 runs,
first ball, dot ball,
new bowler Vivek,
five balls, 23 runs, next ball,
good ball from Vivek towards the pavilion and this was a clean
bowled, it was an
incoming ball, it completely deceived the
batsman,
and you guys please pay some attention to the score board.
Seven runs and seven wickets.
This is also a wonder in itself.
Seven for double thala for region.  But he
can say Alliance Strikers they are
playing for reason.   The
match is his name.  Now Alliance Front
Warriors can say that ind Front Warriors should have scored
23 runs in four balls,
all four should have been big hits but those
too were dot balls,
so this match is in the name of Priors.   Yes,
Mitesh was
completely in his bag, 23 runs in three overs, the
next ball
was a good ball from Vivek,
inside edge one run,
now two balls 22 runs, the
match has become almost impossible, Vivek had
qualified in Group A,
Titans were admitted in the quarter finals
and what happened,
caught and bowled, caught and bowled again
eight wickets for eight runs, that sequence is still going on.
What is the matter.  Eight for eight, the ball stuck to his hands.  It was
as if Feviquick was stuck on their hands.   Yes
Mitesh,
I think this is why the ball is stuck.
This is the lowest score of this tournament.
Yes absolutely 8 for 8
what a match what a match last ball just a
formality to complete and Prudent
Warriors well qualified in the quarter
finals how done already qualified in the
quarter finals
ok so supporters of Prudent Warriors are
you ready and with this this match will not have to
stop, will have to wait a little
they say
enjoy the wait
absolutely enjoy it
and this ball is a free hit
chain for eight free hit ball some runs will be made here
double date ball a good ball again
tried to bowl in the block hole but a
little
V Priors clear victory from Alliance
Strikers once again a big applause for
the Prudent Warriors
and their